<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gershom Tripp</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gershom Tripp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How About That Weather!? - An EDA of Climate Change in Berlin.</title>
      <link>/blog/how-about-that-weather-an-eda-of-climate-change-in-berlin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/how-about-that-weather-an-eda-of-climate-change-in-berlin/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Data Import and Preparation Importing Tidying  Visualizing Climate Change in Berlin Average Annual Temperature Change: Berlin Average Annual Temperature: Global vs. Local  Proportion of +25°C Days Sunshine Precipitation Days Without Precipitation Air Pressure  Conclusion   Introduction The following exploratory data analysis of climate change in Berlin represents a first step in bringing this often abstract issue closer to home. Why is this necessary? Per Espen Stoknes writes the following about the role of psychological “distance” when it comes to inaction in the face of climate change in his book What We Think About When We Try Not to Think About Global Warming:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>colophon</title>
      <link>/about/colophon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 06:28:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/colophon/</guid>
      <description>This website is my personal hompage and blogfolio. I put mostly data-science-related content here, because that&amp;rsquo;s my passion, but sometimes I also write about other things.
Because this is a blog cum portfolio you will often find prose interspersed with code. This is known as literate programming, and I hope it encourages readers/data scientists to learn from, teach, and otherwise interact with me.
The site is built with Hugo—a static site generator made with Go.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>